<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<individual_metafile xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" 
    xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="http://www.cems.uwe.ac.uk/~p-chatterjee/2016-17/modules/dsa/assignment/schemas/individual_metafile_schema.xsd">
    <!-- This file is an example of a valid individual metadata file. 
    Use this example file as a template and update with your own data 
    validating as you go along using Oxygen or some other schema aware editor -->    
    <group id="V"/>
    <student id="16032793"/>
    <!--- List of at least one, possibly more, individual component you worked on  -->
    <component type="Photo Widget">
        <description> I chose to implement flickr api as part of the individual task.
            In this task, flickr api is used to fetch photos relating a country or a region.
            The photos should be shown on the main page of the application.
            When mouse hovers a marker on the map, the application should check for the cookie associated with the country or the region hovered. 
            If cookie does not exist, flickr api should be called to fetch photos and store those photos locally in a variable. 
            Otherwise, photos should be fetched locally from the variable that stores them. 
            Cookie is set to expire after 2 minutes.
        </description>
        <problems> I tried to use php for flickr api. But I had difficulty in getting the country or region information.
            Mouse hover is handled by javascript on the browser side, but flickr is used on the server side.
            So, I could not make it possible to pass information from javascript to php.
        </problems>
        <solutions> Finally, I came up with the idea of fetch flickr api using javascript.
            I used ajax to get json from flickr api and handled it on the browser side.
            After getting photo data as json (using ajax), I managed to append HTML elements to the info windows to display the photos.
        </solutions>
        <hours_effort>8</hours_effort>
        <!-- This should be an URL to the working component - maybe part of the base page -->
        <base_url>http://www.cems.uwe.ac.uk/~kd2-phung/dsa/assignment_individual/index.php</base_url>
        <technologies>
            <tech>php</tech>
            <tech>javascript</tech>
            <tech>html5</tech>
        </technologies>
        <source_files>
            <file>
                <name>main.js</name>
                <purpose>codes were added to this file to fetch flickr photos</purpose>
                <source_url>http://www.cems.uwe.ac.uk/~kd2-phung/dsa/assignment_individual/js/main.js</source_url>
            </file>
            <file>
                <name>index.php</name>
                <purpose>main page with embedded photos</purpose>
                <source_url>http://www.cems.uwe.ac.uk/~kd2-phung/dsa/assignment_individual/index.phps</source_url>
            </file>
        </source_files>
    </component>
    <individual_comment> This part is quite confusing with the flickr api.
        I had to read the documentation several times to understand how to get the address of a photo.
        Generally, this part is interesting when images just show up in the info windows when the marker is hovered.
    </individual_comment>
</individual_metafile>
<!-- DSA Individual Metadata File Example, 2016-17 -->
<!-- author: Khoa2.Phung@live.uwe.ac.uk -->
